<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="47"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[FLIPBUILDER.COM                 FLIP SHOPPING CATALOG























                         Create Professional flipping digital Catalog with PDF]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   About Flip Shopping Catalog





                   Flip  Shopping  Catalog  is  helping  to  build  digital


                   catalogs  with  realistic  page-flipping  effect.  It


                   provides  a  new  and  interesting  way  to  promote


                   and sell products online. The Flip Shopping Catalog


                   program  is  easy-to-use,  and  will  help  to  build  a

                   shopping book within minutes, output to multiple


                   formats you can use, like HTML to publish online,


                   ZIP  or Burn  to  CD  to  send  to  clients,  EXE to  play


                   individually  in  your  store,  mobile  version  enables


                   users to view on iPhone, iPad and Android devices.


                   The  wonderful  look  digital  catalogs  will  definitely


                   impress your clients with so many interactive and


                   powerful features.






                     Note:  This  product  is  distributed  on  a  "Try  before-you-buy"

                     basis.  All  features  described  in  this  documentation  are


                     enabled. The registered version doesn't insert a watermark in


                     your generated page-flipping eBooks.





                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 1 -]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   Product features





                       1.  Convert  PDF  to  Adobe©   Flash®  based  digital  shopping  catalogs  with

                          page-flipping effect.

                       2.  Batch convert multiple PDF files to a single or multiple page-flipping eBooks.

                       3.  Provide command line version.

                       4.  Import bookmarks (outline) with PDF, and edit them manually.

                       5.  Import hyperlinks with PDF, include web link, page link, email link.
                       6.  Import text so text is searchable, define the minimum search characters.

                       7.  Detect landscape page to present as two-page spread.

                       8.  Add watermarks text, image, dynamic date/ time etc to page-flipping eBooks.

                       9.  Define quality and size for normal version and mobile version.

                       10. Detect landscape page to present as two-page spread.
                       11. Output in different formats: HTML, EXE, Zip, Mac App, Mobile version and Burn

                          to CD.

                          o     HTML allows you to upload to a website to be viewed online (with title,

                          keywords and other metadata defined).

                          o     EXE (with setting title, icon and open window size) and Zip allow you to

                          send to your user by email to be viewed on their computer.

                          o     App (Mac Application) is executable application can be run on Mac.

                          o     Mobile version is to output HTML flipbook which can be viewed on mobile

                          devices via Browsers.
                          o     Burn to CD allows you to burn to disk so you can send your user physical

                          media for viewing on their computer.

                       12. Apply a pre-designed template.

                       13. Preview the output effect instantly.

                       14. Add HTML Title in Float template which can be clicked to visit webpage online.

                       15. Add Image or Flash logo to insert before Book Title in Float template.

                       16. Define book proportions, margin size, shadow manually.
                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 2 -]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                       17. Replace existing icons on toolbar by editing Icon Flash file.

                       18. Add new icons into toolbar with calling new actions.

                       19. Set background color and image.

                       20. Insert background music either for continuous play (loop) or for a set duration.

                       21. Set eBook reading from right to left (for Right-to-Left languages such as Arabic).

                       22. Choose hard cover for eBooks.

                       23. Set fonts for Flash and Bookmark, Search panel.

                       24. Set Page Number Box to show at top or bottom in Float, set start page number.

                       25. Add  shopping  projects  to  pages,  like  Price,  Order  buttons,  Product  photos,
                          Shopping icons, etc.


                       26. Edit pages with embedding links, images, movies, flash, sound or You Tube video
                          files.

                       27. Add Button on pages to open link page, call Javascript action, play Flash/Video in

                          pop-up Window.

                       28. Copy projects from one page to another or all the other pages.

                       29. Define  the  language  for  your  published  page-flipping  eBook  (support

                          multi-language show and switchable).

                       30. Add password to protect your page-flipping eBook.

                       31. Add Google Analytics Support.

                       32. Add watermark image or SWF to show on print out pages.

                       33. Add Help config to manually define content with using Image or SWF.

                       34. Add Single/Double Page view.
                       35. Add Minime Style to show page-flipping eBooks without toolbar.


                       36. Set permissions for downloading, printing, social sharing, Home, About button
                          and more.

                       37. Edit bookmark manually and set bookmark panel to show on left or right side.

                       38. Export and save settings for future uses.

                       39. Save and Load your project.



                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 3 -]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   Page-flipping eBook features





                   With the page-flipping ebook you have created, your user will be able to:


                       1.  Show Product Shopping Catalog online with page-turning effect.

                       2.  Click button, link, and text on pages to go to product or order web pages.

                       3.  Drag the corner or page frame to flip pages.

                       4.  Click navigation buttons on toolbar to turn pages.
                       5.  Input password to unlock encrypted pages.


                       6.  Single/Double Page view.
                       7.  View with pre-loading needed pages to open quickly, do not need to wait all

                          pages loaded.

                       8.  Use button to control page, such as Previous, Next, First, Last etc.

                       9.  Flip pages automatically.

                       10. View flipbook repeatedly.

                       11. View page-flipping ebook full screen.

                       12. Use thumbnail to navigate.

                       13. Search whole eBook.

                       14. Print out the whole ebook or a range of pages directly (support to clip area on

                          pages and then print).

                       15. Download the uploaded page-flipping eBook from web site directly.
                       16. Double-click to zoom in or zoom out.


                       17. Zoom in/ out both pages.
                       18. Share eBook url via email.

                       19. Open or close page-turning sound.

                       20. Open  to  a  certain  page  in  Browser  by  adding  a  suffix  like  this:

                          index.html?pageIndex=4.

                       21. View output page-flipping eBook on iPad, iPhone and Android devices (slide

                          single pages mode supported).

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 4 -]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   Quick Start







                   1. Launch the application via the desktop shortcut             ;




                   2. Click the "Import" icon             to enter into Import PDF interface;


                   3. Click             icon to choose PDF file from your computer;


                   4. Click              icon to enter into template setting interface;


                   5.  Edit  shopping  page  objects,  define  parameters  for  eBooks,  such  as




                   Book, Tool Bar, Bookmarks, and then click the "Apply Change" icon                ;




                   6.  Click  "Convert  to  Flipping  Book"  icon           to  enter  into  Output

                   interface;


                   7.  Choose  Output  Type  from  HTML,  ZIP  and  EXE,  here  take





                                   as example;

                   8. Click             to set Output Folder as "C:\flipbook", input File Name


                   as "demo";


                   9. At last, click           icon to output created page-flipping eBook.




                   You can open the "flipbook" folder in "C:", there are three files in this folder:









                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 5 -]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   Open  the  "demo.html"  file  to  view  your  created  p00age-flipping  book  via  Web
                   Browser, such as Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Firefox, etc.









































                   Interfaces




                   There are some main interfaces you will see while using Flip Shopping


                   Catalog  as  below  shows:  Application  Options,  Import  PDF,  Template


                   Settings,  Edit  Pages,  Language  Option,  Export  Theme,  Output,  Batch


                   Convert and Command Line.


                   You can enter into each page to get clear instructions for every detail


                   option.







                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 6 -]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                     I.  Application Options Interface



                   1. Render Engine Option


                   Flip Shopping Catalog provides 3 different render engines for you to create higher
                   quality page-flipping eBooks (change option when PDF imported failed), click
                   "Options->Application Options" to enter into "Render Engine" interface:
                   SWF: Much legible characters, smaller output size
                   GPL Ghostscript: Higher color transfer quality
                   Inner Library: Faster convert speed

































                   2. Create Mobile Version Option

                   (1) Pages Quality and Size
                   Five types of "Pages Quality And Size" for mobile version eBooks:











                   (2) Mobile Template
                   The current version provides two mobile template modes for you to use: Slide and
                   Single Page Flip. The later one adds page-flipping effect on the pages while viewing
                   in mobiles.
                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 7 -]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                    II.  Import PDF Interface







































                   1. Source PDF File:

                                Click this icon to open the PDF file you want to convert;


                                View content of added PDF file to clarify before converting.


                   2. The Page Ranges to Import:


                                Convert all pages to page-flipping eBook;


                                                                Convert defined range page;


                                                                 Just preview effect on first 10 pages.


                   3. Watermark


                                  Add image or text watermark to flipping pages.


                                     Check this option first to choose default stamps or add new ones:



                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 8 -]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document






































                   4. Page Quality
                   There are five types of "Quality And Size":










                   5. Other Options:


                                   If  your  PDF  file  contains  bookmarks,  check  this  option  to  use  in  output

                   page-flipping eBook;

                                   If your PDF file has links, check this to enable in flipbook;


                                   Check this option to enable search functionality in created flipbook.


                                     Check this option to make landscape page in PDF file to be presented as
                   two-page spread in output flipbook.


                   At last, click                icon to enter into template setting interface.

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                           - 9 -]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   III.  Template Settings Interface






























                   The design setting interface contains below main parts: Choose Template, Tool Bars
                   Settings, Flash Display Settings and Flash Control Settings.



                   1. Choose Template









                   Click                      icon to select templates from below interface:






















                   Download more themes from FlipBuilder now:
                   http://www.flipbuilder.com/templates-themes/theme.html .

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 10 -]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document


                           Click this icon is to save current settings as a TXT file for later uses;


                           Click this icon is to import stored setting file at once.


                   2. Tool Bar Settings











                   (1) Title Bar (only in Float template)










                   Customize book title and logo for showing on the top of your flipbook. You are enabled to
                   set the book title as HTML format text. For example: <a href='http://www.flipbuilder.com'
                   target='_blank'>FLIPBUILDER.COM</a> | <font color='#ff0000' size='14'>Red Color</font>


                   (2) Buttons Bar

























                   i. Home Button

                   You can add a home button     to help reader to click and go to your website directly:


                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 11 -]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document







                   ii. About Button

                   Add About button     to show the author, contact, book, company info:





                   Click "…" to enter into "About & Contact" edit interface:





















                   After clicking the About button, you will view the About window by clicking the button:



















                   iii. Full Screen Button
                   To  enable  "Full  Screen"  functionality  in  output  flipbook,  select  "Show"  in  "Full  Screen

                   Button" option:

                   Then you can click icon       to view flipbook in Full Screen, click icon     or "Esc"
                   button to exit from the Full Screen.
                   Or if you want to show your flipbook without Tool Bar while showing in Full Screen mode,
                   you  can  set  "No"  in  "Full  Screen  without  Tool  Bar"  (just  in  Classical  Template):

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 12 -]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   iv. Help Config









                   To show tips about viewing flipbook, you can set "Show" in "Help Button" option, and you
                   can  define  Help  Content  manually  by  inserting  "Help  Content  File  (image  or  SWF)",  also
                   enable to define the Width and Height of the Help image or swf. If you set "Book->Retain the
                   book to center->No", you can set "Show Help At First->Show" to display the Help Panel with
                   the Book as below:
























                   You can also click the button     to view the same Help page in pop-up window.



                   v. Print Config






                   Choose "Yes" in "Print Enable", then click icon     to set print page range as below:















                   You can also click "Print Watermark File->…" button to choose image or SWF file from your
                   computer as watermark on printed out pages.

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 13 -]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   vi. Download Setting





                   If you want your flipbook readers to download the PDF file or the flipbook directly from your
                   website, select "Yes" in "Download Enable" option, then input the Download URL directly,
                   you can use absolute path like
                   "http://www.flipbuilder.com/flip-pdf/example/files/download/FlipPDFDemo.pdf" or relative
                   path like "/files/download/FlipPDFDemo.pdf" (make sure you have uploaded the PDF to the
                   same path).


                   Then readers can click the icon      to download your uploaded PDF file directly.


                   vii. Sound





                   If you want to add background sound to your flipbook, such as a song or other audio file, set
                   "Enable Sound->Enable", then click "  " icon to choose "Sound File" from your computer,
                   then  set  "Sound  Loops", "-1"  stands  for  playing  the  sound  file  all the  time  while  viewing
                   flipbook, other value (N>0) stands for the times of playing the sound file.


                   viii. Zoom Config






















                   To Enable Zoon In functionality, choose ''Yes" in "Zoon in enable", then set "Zoom Scale", the
                   value is the times between zoomed page size and the current page size.

                   In Float template, you don't need to set Zoom Scale, you can adjust more conveniently by


                   the zoom in tool like this:                                  . You can also set "Scroll
                   with mouse->Yes" to scroll zoom in page while moving mouse.
                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 14 -]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   ix. Search





                   Select  "Show"  in  "Search  Button"  (make  sure  you  have  check  "Enable  Search"  option  in
                   "Import PDF"  interface), then  define  "Search  Highlight  Color",  after  clicking  "Search"  icon

                          , you will see a popup box to input search words, then click Enter or "Search" button,
                   you will get the below searching result:















                   x. Share





                   You can share via emails, or just through Facebook, Twitter, Google, etc..

                   a. Share Button
                   If you want readers to share via Email, you can enable "Share" feature as below shows:






                   When the viewers click the share button    , they will enter into the Email interface with

                   the link of your flipbook in the Email body.


                   b. Social Share
                   If you want your flipbook viewers to send the link to their friends or clients via Facebook,
                   Twitter,  Linkedin,  Google,  Yahoo  and  so  on,  you  can  add  a  Social  Share  button  in  your
                   flipbook for readers to send out your flipbook link immediately:


                   The readers just need to click the "Social Share" button  , then the below window will pop

                   up for them to choose share channel:




                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 15 -]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document

















                   xi. Auto Flip
                   To auto flip your eBooks, you can set "Yes" in "Auto Flip->Enable" option; then define the
                   Flip Interval (seconds of staying on each page); the value of "Play Count" stands for the times
                   of auto playing the eBook, and "-1" stands for playing forever (after clicking the Auto Flip


                   button      , the flipbooks will be flipped by staying 3 seconds per page); if you want to
                   auto start and flip the eBook after opening, just set "Auto flip when start up->Yes":









                   xii. Thumbnail Button



                   Show Thumbnail Button     (set "Enable") to view page thumbnails of your book, or you can
                   Disable it to hide the button.


                   xiii. Single Page

                   If your book contains landscape pages, or the page content is different to read for the font is too


                   small, you can set "Single Page->Enable" to enable readers to click "Single Page" icon     to


                   view pages one after another, then click "Double Page" icon     to back to the normal book
                   reading mode.


                   (3) Tool Bar on Top (only in Float template)
                   If you want to place the toolbar in Float templates on the top of the flash eBook, you can set
                   "Tool Bar on Top" as "True":



                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 16 -]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
















                   (4) Add Icons Settings
                   If you want to add some other kinds of buttons which the program doesn't provide, you can click
                   "Add Icons Settings->…" to enter into "Icons Settings" interface to add new icons on tool bar:





































                   You  can  define  the  link  action  as  "Go  to  page",  or  open  an  online  webpage,  or  even  "Call
                   Javascript function" to carry  out your wanted interactive  functionalities via defining Javascript
                   function yourself.. After your "Apply Change", the new added icon will show in the toolbar. (More
                   details about Call Javascript function will be introduced in the part of "Edit Page->Add Link".)


                   (5) Button Icons
                   Define settings for the icons of the buttons:







                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 17 -]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   i. Icon Color







                   ii. Icon File
                   Select the Tool Bar Button to replace with your own icon.

                   More details please view here:
                   http://www.flipbuilder.com/support/how-to-replace-icons-on-flash-toolbar.htm



                   3. Flash Display Settings























                   (1) Retain the book to center


                   If you select “No” in this option, the eBook will be shown on the right-side. This setting is for
                   embedding special background image, such as advertisement or company log.

                   (2) Language



                   You  can  set  language  for  showing  tools  or  tips  in  your  created  flipbook,  and  here  is  the
                   specialized instruction page for setting the "Language Option".

                   (3) Font











                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 18 -]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   If you want to change fonts of toolbar buttons, flash windows even bookmarks or search
                   result panel, you can set font types and colors in Font Panel.


                   (4) Initial Show (set in Float/ Spread templates)
                   You can show Bookmark panel or Thumbnails panel on the flash page at the beginning, just
                   select "Bookmark" or "Thumbnails" in this option:

                   For Example, select "Thumbnails":

                   Then you will get flipbook shown with below initial interface:
























                   (5) Background Config

                   i. Background Color:



















                   Define background for your flipbook with gradient color or pure color (the same color for
                   "Gradient Color A" and "Gradient Color B"). Gradient Angle is the angle between the two
                   colors.







                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 19 -]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   ii. Background Image (set in Classical and Spread templates):















                   Click the icon "  " to choose background image from your computer, and there are 11 kinds
                   of  "Image  Position"  for  you  to  choose:  Scale  to  fit,  Fill,  Top  Left,  Top  Center,  Top  Right,
                   Middle Left, Middle Center, Middle Right, Bottom Left, Bottom Center and Bottom Right.

                   iii. Background Image (set in Float template):

















                   The  Float  template  enables  you  to  add  two  background  images:  Outer  Image  and  Inner
                   Image.  You  can  make  Inner  background  image  to  show  special  information,  such  as
                   advertisement or company logo, etc. There are also 11 kinds of "Image Position" for you to
                   choose: Scale to fit, Fill, Top Left, Top Center, Top Right, Middle Left, Middle Center, Middle
                   Right, Bottom Left, Bottom Center and Bottom Right


                   (6) Flash Window Color
















                   This color will be applied on all flash windows, such as the book window, "Help" window,
                   "Print" window and so on.



                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 20 -]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   (7) Page Background Color


















                   When load pages, or if the page number of your PDF file is odd, then the page (the last page)
                   will show with the "Page Background Color".


                   (8) Book Proportions



















                   Please note that the values are not fixed in pixels or inches, they just represent a ratio for
                   "Page  Width:  Page  Height",  and  the  book  size  will  be  changed  depend  on  your  Explorer
                   Window Size.


                   (9) Book Margins

                   i. Book Margin (set in Classical Template):

















                   "Book Margin" refers to the distance between the book and the toolbar.
                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 21 -]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   ii. Top/ Bottom/ Left/ Right Margin (set in Float/ Spread Template):


















                   (10) Page Shadow

















                   The value also takes the value of Book Proportions as reference, and the value interval of
                   "Page Shadow Opacity" is "0~1", the larger value refers to the deeper shadow color.


                   (11) Hide Book Frame Bar



                   If don’t want to show the book frame bar, choose “Yes” in this option.


                   (12) Right to Left
                   If the language of your file is read from right to left (such as Arabic), then choose "Yes" in
                   "Right to Left" option:

















                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 22 -]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   (13) Hard Cover
                   If you want create hard cover effect (a book bound with rigid protective covers) for your
                   flipbook, choose "Yes" in "Hard Cover" option:















                   (14) Flipping time


                   Sets page flipping time in seconds according to needs. (Recommended second value is 0.6)



                   (15) Page Number
                   If you don't want to count in the cover page, table of contents pages into the actual page
                   numbers, you can set "Start Page Numbering (Roman)" and "Start Page Numbering (Arabic)".
                   For example, the first 3 pages are Table of Content pages with Roman page numbers, and
                   set Arabic page numbers from page 4, then you will get page number box like below:













                   (16) Minime Style
                   To present Page-flipping eBook pages directly without showing toolbar, especially when you want
                   to embed eBook into a small area in existing webpages, then you can use this "Minime Style":





















                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 23 -]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   The Minime Style will trigger when the Width or Height of the Flash Container is less than the
                   defined value. You can also always show the page-flipping eBook in Minime Style with adding a
                   parameter to your URL like this: www.yourdomain.com/index.html?alwaysMinimeStyle=true .


                   4. Flash Control Settings






                   (1). Security Settings



                   If you want to protect your flash books with passwords, you can click "…" icon to enter into
                   "Flash Security Config" interface:




















                   Select  "Security  Type->Single  Password",  and  input  passwords  into  the  box  (there  is  no
                   restriction on password format at present). You can also set "Protect Page Range" as "All
                   Pages"  or  the  latter  pages  after  a  defined  page  number.  (Tips:  The  program  utilize  RC4
                   algorithm  to  protect  eBook  pages,  the  eBook  content  pages  will  show  nothing  without
                   permission.)


                   (2). Links



















                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 24 -]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   If you have check "Import links" option in "Import PDF" interface, or add links in "Edit Page"
                   interface, then you can define settings here, choose "Mouse over color", "Link alpha" (refers
                   to the link area opacity, value interval: 0~1, "0" stands for the area is totally transparent),
                   and  "Open  Window->Blank/  Self".  The  links  also  can  be  clicked  after  zooming  by  setting
                   "Enable after Zooming in->Enable".


                   (3). Google Analytics


                   In the HTML output format, you can add statistics by using google analytics. You can get
                   more information about Google Analytics ID from http://www.google.com/analytics/ .



                   Besides, Export Theme

                   If you want to save the current template settings as your own style template for later uses,
                   you can click "File->Export current settings as Theme" button to storing all current template
                   settings, include the background images, margin values, toolbar buttons and so on.
                   Then when you want to use later, just click "File->Import Themes", the theme will be added
                   to the templates selecting interface. Download more themes from FlipBuilder now:
                   http://www.flipbuilder.com/templates-themes/theme.html .




                   IV.  Edit Pages


                   Now you can use Flip Shopping Catalog to edit imported pages directly, no matter you want to
                   add shopping price, item, product detail photos slideshow, link, video, sound or image file. Just


                   click "Edit Pages" button              to enter into the editing interface:

























                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 25 -]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   1. Text Button

                   Click the icon     and then draw a button on a page, then define properties in below panel:


























                   Define Button Text, set link URL, there are many different action options, like Go to page, Open a
                   link, Call Javascript function, Open Flash window, Play Audio and Play Slideshow.

                   2. Price Icon




                   Click "Price" icon   to add price for products like this:

                   You can also edit the icon type yourself in Properties panel:



































                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 26 -]]></page><page Index="28"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   3. Add Product Photos


                   Click "Product Photos" icon    to add images to pop-up in slideshow format:






























                   4. Add Button from Resources
                   Flip Shopping Catalog also provides many nice and typical resources for you to use on ebooks.


                   Click icon    to add the icons onto pages, you can also use your own icons:





























                   5. Add Link


                   Click the icon      and then draw a link box on the area you want to add link, then define
                   properties in below panel:
                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 27 -]]></page><page Index="29"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
























                   You  can  define  the  link  action  as  "Go  to  page",  or  open  an  online  webpage,  or  even  "Call
                   Javascript function"  to carry  out your  wanted interactive  functionalities via defining Javascript
                   function yourself.. For example,  you can  show a pop-up light box while  readers clicking some
                   image on page, or pop-up a questionnaire or other Web Form by clicking some text. Just make
                   sure the parameter you set in "Function" can be called in from HTML page.

                   Example:  Check  "Call  Javascript  function"  as  action  type,  then  input  Function  as
                   "testLightBox("Hello, this is a test"):





























                   And then make sure the Javascript wrote into the index.html page as below image shows (the
                   same as you set in "Link Function"):








                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 28 -]]></page><page Index="30"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document






























                   6. Add Movie


                   Click icon      and then draw a box like below on the page you want to insert FLV movie:







                   Then you can select and edit the movie in below panel (define video player skin color, play and
                   stop movie actions, etc.):
























                   7. Add Image


                   Click icon      to draw image box and then select image (.jpg, .png, .bmp), set Action Options:


                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 29 -]]></page><page Index="31"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document




















                   8. Add Sound


                   Click the icon     to draw sound box and then select sound file, set other options:





















                   9. Add Flash


                   Click icon      to insert SWF flash into your defined area of flipbook page:


























                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 30 -]]></page><page Index="32"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   10. Add Button

                   Click icon     to draw an area for inserting your image or SWF button file with calling actions.

                   The  actions  contain  "Go  to  page",  "Open  a  link",  "Call  Javascript  function"  and  "Open  Flash
                   Window". The before three actions are the same with the actions in "Add Link", the "Open Flash
                   Window" can help you to play SWF Flash or FLV Video in the pop-up window:





























                   11. Add You Tube Video

                   Click the icon   and then draw a box on the page to insert You Tube video into pages directly.

                   You  just  need  to  define  the  video  ID  directly.  For  example  the  video  link  is:
                   http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xKA6WIqjB7c, then the video ID is "xKA6WIqjB7c".




























                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 31 -]]></page><page Index="33"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   12. Add Printable Area
                   If  you  want  readers  can  click  on  some  area  of  your  book  to  print  the  area  directly,  such  as
                   coupons which can be used to buy  your presented goods, you can add a "Printable Area" on

                   pages by clicking the icon  , and then draw the area on the pages, set title and description:



























                   13. Copy and Paste
                   If you want to add same links, images, videos, audios to different pages, you don't have to repeat
                   the "Link/Image/Video/Audio added" operations once and once again, just select the link object,

                   click the copy button   and then go to the other page to click the paste button   directly.



                   14. Apply All
                   If you want to use the same link, video, audio, image or button on all pages (or all odd, even
                   pages, or your customized pages), you can select the object and then click the Apply All button

                       , then define the apply page range in pop-up window like below:

















                   After adding links, flash, movie or sounds, you can click the icon    to save the settings and
                   back to the template setting interface.

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 32 -]]></page><page Index="34"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                    V.  Language Options Interface



                   Click "Option->Flash Language", you will enter into the Language Settings interface as below
                   shows:































                   Panel Description:

                   As the tips explaining, the "Labeled" column lists the buttons and instructions on Flash books
                   in defined language, and the program provides you five different languages for you to use:
                   English, Chinese Arabic, French and Greek.









                   You can also add other language for your own uses:


                   1. Click the button                and define name for the new language:














                   Click "OK" to save the new language in the list;

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 33 -]]></page><page Index="35"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   2. Choose the first label and click "Edit" icon, define new language text in "Labeled" box,
                   then click "Save And Edit Next":























                   3. At last, you can get all Labels translated into your new language as the images shows:




















                   You can delete unwanted language:


                   Or save your edited new language file as XML or TXT file:


                   Load language file saving before for current using:





                   After  setting  template  and  language,  click                            icon  to


                   apply the settings.








                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 34 -]]></page><page Index="36"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   VI.  Output Interface













































                   Output types:





                   1. HTML





                   This output type is for uploading created page-flipping ebook onto websites:

                   You can define HTML Title and other properties by clicking "Advanced" button:







                   Set Keywords, Description or even Script in the below interface:

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 35 -]]></page><page Index="37"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document




























                   2. ZIP





                   This output type is for compressing the created files into an integral ZIP package which can
                   be  sending  out  as  attachment  directly.  You  can  also  define  HTML  Advanced  Settings  by


                   clicking "Advanced" icon:

                   Your  recipients  just  need  to  uncompress  the  ZIP  file  and  then  they  can  view  the  HTML
                   flipbook instantly:











                   3. EXE




                   This type is for outputting flipbook as a single executive file, easy storing and easy viewing:







                   You can also define Icon and Opening Window Size in Advanced Settings:
                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 36 -]]></page><page Index="38"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document




















                   4. APP





                   If  you  want  to  make  executable  application  to  run  on  Mac  devices,  you  can  output  as
                   "*.app" format.


                   5. Mobile Version


                   You can even output Mobile Version while choosing HTML or ZIP format at the same time.
                   After creating mobile versions, you just need to output all files online (including HTML, SWF,
                   "files"  and  "mobile"  folders),  then  you  can  visit  the  flipbook  page  through  your  mobile
                   browser.


                   6. Burn to CD










                   After  choosing output  type,  then  check  the option "Burn  to  CD",  set  "CD  Writer",  define
                   "Disc title".

                   How to make created eBooks available for others online,  more details this support page:
                   http://flipbuilder.com/support/how-can-i-share-my-created-ebook-online.htm .


                   At last click             button to output flipbook in your defined type.



                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 37 -]]></page><page Index="39"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                  VII.  Batch Convert Interface

































                   1. Add PDF Documents

                             Click this icon to add PDF files from computer;


                                Click this icon to add all PDF files in the folder (include sub-folders).


                   You can also remove some unwanted PDF, move up/ down files, or clear all documents.




                   2. Settings



                   (1). Output Settings

                     i. Choose Output Type






                     ii. Choose Output Path





                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 38 -]]></page><page Index="40"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   You can also define output name pattern with FileName, Title, Subject and so on:








                   And after defining the File Name, you can preview the result example below:







                     iii. Define Output Option







                   Click "Advanced" icon to define Keywords, Description for HTML flipbooks, or define Icon,
                   Window Size for EXE flipbooks:



















                     iv. Merge All PDF Files to One Flip Book




                   (2). PDF Settings

                     i. Page Range








                   You can convert "All pages" or just "Custom range";



                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 39 -]]></page><page Index="41"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                     ii. Watermark







                   Click "Set Watermark" icon to enter into "Watermark" interface:


























                   Check "Applying Watermark" option, then you can choose default stamps, Edit them, or Add
                   Text Watermark, Add Image Watermark, Delete, Move Down/ Up.

                     iii. Page Quality









                   Choose quality and size type from listed five kinds.

                     iv. Other Options


                                  If  your  PDF  file  contains  bookmarks,  check  this  option  to  use  in  output

                   page-flipping eBook;

                                  If your PDF file has links, check this to enable in flipbook;


                                   Check this option to enable search functionality in created flipbook.



                   At last, click                      icon to batch convert listed files together.


                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 40 -]]></page><page Index="42"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                 VIII.  Use Flip Shopping Catalog in Command Line



                   You can also use Flip Shopping Catalog in Command Line.




                   Flip Shopping Catalogfessional Command Line Usage:

                     PTCMD.exe [Options]

                     -f<PDF File>                      The source PDF file.

                     -o<output folder>            Specify the folder for the output files.

                     -t[html|zip|exe]              Output type. Default is html.

                     -n<OutputFileName>      Specify the name for the output file.

                     -c<caption>                      Caption for HTML or EXE.

                     -s<Flash settings>            Value format is:<Template name>#[<Theme name>|
                                             <txt_settingfile path>].
                                             <Template name> could be: Classic, Float, Spread.
                                             <Theme name> are list in the "Select a template" window,
                                             such as Blank,Blues,Nostalgia.
                                             <txt_settingfile path> is the file that you export
                                             with "Save the template settings" function

                     -r<page range>.         The page range that you want to import from PDF File.
                                             Range value string like:2-15,33,35-36,or All.(Default: All)

                     -q<import quality>        Count be 5,4,3,2,1.5 specify the higher quality larger file
                                             size;1 specifies lower quality smaller file size.(default:4)

                   -R<GS|SWF|LIB>           Render  engine  options.  (Default:  GS,  Ghostscript  render
                   engine)

                     -b<Y|N>                          Import bookmark yes or no. (Default: Y)

                     -l<Y|N>                         Import links yes or no. (Default: Y).

                     -S<Y|N>                          Enable searchable or not.(Default: Y, enable searchable)

                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 41 -]]></page><page Index="43"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                     -k<html key words>        Set the keywords for html output file.

                     -d<html description>      Set the descriptions for html output file.

                     -j<html javascript>          Set the javascript for html output file.

                     -i<icon file path>            Specify the icon path for exe output.

                     -w<window size>            Specify the size of exe window.
                                              Value could be: M,F, or some string like:800,600.
                                             (width is 800,height is 600).


                     Examples 1:
                     PTCMD -f"C:\input.pdf" -o"C:\outputfolder" -n"index" -thtml -c"Title"
                   -s"Float#c:\my_ebooksetting.txt" -r"1-8,9-14,42" -q4 -R"SWF" -bN

                     Examples 2:
                     PTCMD  -f"C:\input.pdf"  -o"C:\outputfolder"  -n"ExeFileName"  -texe  -i"C:\app.ico"
                   -c"Title" -s"Float#Blues" -r"All" -q5 -R"GS"

                     Examples 3:
                     PTCMD     -f"C:\input.pdf"   -o"C:\outputfolder"    -n"index"    -tzip   -c"Title"
                   -s"Float#Blank" -r"All" -q5 -R"GS" -k"html key words"\


                   Return Code:
                   1:    Success
                   2:    Input file not found
                   3:    Parameters are invalid
                   4:    Failed to load PDF
                   5:    Failed to import bookmarks
                   6:    Failed to import links
                   7:    Failed to import searchable information
                   8:    Failed to save the output file.











                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 42 -]]></page><page Index="44"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   License Agreements





                   All copyrights to Flip Shopping Catalog (the Software) are exclusively owned by
                   FlipBuilder.com. For more information, visit our website at www.Flipbuilder.com .

                   Anyone may use this software but all the page-flipping eBooks generated will automatically
                   have a demo watermark on the first page of them. To remove the limitation you must
                   register.

                   Once registered, the user is granted a non-exclusive license to use the Software on one
                   computer (i.e. a single CPU) at a time. The registered Software may not be rented or leased,
                   but may be permanently transferred, if the person receiving it agrees to terms of this
                   license.

                   The Software unregistered (trial) version may be freely distributed, provided the distribution
                   package is not modified. No person or company may charge a fee for the distribution of the
                   Software without written permission from the copyright holder.

                   THE SOFTWARE IS DISTRIBUTED "AS IS". NO WARRANTY OF ANY KIND IS EXPRESSED OR
                   IMPLIED. YOU USE AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE AUTHOR WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DATA LOSS,
                   DAMAGES, LOSS OF PROFITS OR ANY OTHER KIND OF LOSS WHILE USING OR MISUSING THIS
                   SOFTWARE.

                   You may not use, copy, emulate, clone, rent, lease, sell, modify, decompile, disassemble,
                   otherwise reverse engineer, or transfer the licensed Software, or any subset of the licensed
                   Software, except as provided for in this agreement. Any such unauthorized use shall result in
                   immediate and automatic termination of this license and may result in criminal and/or civil
                   prosecution.

                   All rights not expressly granted here are reserved by A-PDF Solution.

                   Installing and using the Software signifies acceptance of these terms and conditions of the
                   license.

                   If you do not agree with the terms of this license you must remove the Software files from
                   your storage devices and cease to use the product.







                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 43 -]]></page><page Index="45"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   How to Order







                   Order  Online  (http://www.flipbuilder.com/flip-shopping-catalog/index.html)  or  Order  Toll
                   Free 1-877-353-7297 (When you order toll free just give the operator the product number of
                   the product you would like).

                   How to purchase online?

                   1. Select  a license type above, and click [Buy Now]

                   2. Select  the currency that you want to use. (You can also continue shopping)

                   3. Fill billing information and select a payment method. (Your information is safe with us)

                   4. Check the information you filled previously and click "Place Secure Order"

                   Other Order Ways—With Phone/Mail/Fax/Check:

                   If you are not comfortable ordering online with a credit card, you are welcome to choose an
                   offline order option in the payment section of the order process. We accept mail, fax, wire,
                   and PO  (if applicable) ordering options in addition to ordering online. We also provide
                   phone orders through our 24x7 order desk at 1-877-353-7297, or (952) 646-5331 for
                   International Callers.

                   Please note that all of the offline ordering options do have additional fees for processing. To
                   place an order by mail, fax, wire, and PO (when applicable), use the online form and then
                   choose one of these payment options found in the Payment Method section of the form.
                   Once submitted online, the appropriate information will be provided to you in your web
                   browser to send your payment to us offline.

                   100% unconditional 30 Day Money Back Guarantee


                   Want to custom the program or have other questions about purchase?
                   Contact us at alice@flipbuilder.com .






                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 44 -]]></page><page Index="46"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document
                   Support




                   You can easily search or browse our frequently asked questions, and learn tutorials about
                   products, and get your registration code back. If you are not satisfy with the solutions
                   provided, please contact support team for help.




                   1. Frequently Asked Questions



                   You can find answers to questions about technique issues here:
                   http://www.flipbuilder.com/support




                   2. Get lost license code


                   Click here to look up the order » (http://www.regnow.com/cs/orderStatus)
                   You can pull up a copy of your order by entering your email address. After you find your
                   order, you may view its status, view details of your order (including the license key), and
                   obtain the invoice.



                   3. Contact Us



                   If you have other questions or requirements, contact us directly through our support Email:
                   alice@flipbuilder.com, we will respond you ASAP.


























                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 45 -]]></page><page Index="47"><![CDATA[Convert  PDF  to  Digital  Shopping  Catalog  Utility
                                                                                      User  Document



















































































                                            Copyright 2010 by FlipBuilder.com
                                                          - 46 -]]></page></pages></Search>